[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "What is the name of the web content accessibility guidlines site?",
        "options": [
            "WCAG",
            "WAI",
            "W3C",
            "All of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "WCAG"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "Which of the following is in the main accessibility types?",
        "options": [
            "Eyesight Accessibility",
            "Hearing Accessibility",
            "Keyboard Accessibility",
            "All of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above."
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "What contrast ratio is the standard of a AA rating?",
        "options": [
            "Any ratio",
            "7 : 1",
            "4.5 : 1",
            "21 : 1"
        ],
        "answer": "4.5 : 1"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "What does aria stand for?",
        "options": [
            "Assitive Rich Internet Applications",
            "Assisive Reading In Applications",
            "Archie Reads In Aisles",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "Assitive Rich Internet Applications"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "What features are expected to ensure forms are accessible by assisstive technology?",
        "options": [
            "Labels",
            "Aria tags",
            "Accessible error messages",
            "All of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above."
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "On a website, all images and videos should have ____ text to describe what is being presented?",
        "options": [
            "descriptive",
            "alt",
            "src",
            "aria-label"
        ],
        "answer": "alt"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "What key on the keyboard is used to assess the keyboard accessibility of a website?",
        "options": [
            "Shift",
            "Tab",
            "Ctrl",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "Tab"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "What is the focus of this website?",
        "options": [
            "I don't know.",
            "Teach about Web Accessibility.",
            "To get a good grade.",
            "All of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "Teach about Web Accessibility."
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : "Who can make use of web accessibility?",
        "options": [
            "Developers",
            "Managers",
            "Thomas",
            "Anyone"
        ],
        "answer": "Anyone"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "Why is web accessibility important?",
        "options": [
            "Allows for anyone to access websites.",
            "I'm morally obligated.",
            "I need to be able to access my website?",
            "None of the above."
        ],
        "answer": "Allows for anyone to access websites."
    }
]